ronhazelton.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy • Ron Hazelton Online • DIY Ideas & Projects

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for [http://www.ronhazelton.com](http://www.ronhazelton.com/). Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.

##  Information Collection, Use and Sharing

During your use of this site, we may collect, via the Google Analytics tracking software, information about your computer, including your web browser and version number, operating system, screen resolution and various other details which can help us to design our site to better meet the needs of our viewers. At no time during this automatic information gathering process do we obtain any information which may be used to personally identify you.

We may also collect your email address and/or other personally-identifiable information which you voluntarily give us via email, site registration, newsletter sign-up, or other direct contact from you. We will never sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request (e.g. our consultants and other third party companies we may use in order to deliver your services).

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products, services, or changes to this privacy policy.

##  Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

##  Cookies

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive.

We use a tracking cookie to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Tracking cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a tracking cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

In addition, some of our advertisers, including Google, may use a tracking cookie to track your interests, including which advertisements you have clicked on in the past. They will use this information to provide more relevant advertising to you. We make no warranties, express or implied, to the privacy or security practices of Google and other advertisers. We advise you to check their privacy policies.

One of our partners offers an [opt-out system](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for their anonymous data tracking services, and you can view their opt-out program [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

We will never at any time sell demographic information we may capture on our site.

##  Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be advised that we are not responsible for, nor do we make any express or implied warranties to the content, privacy, or security practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information 

_If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, contact us immediately via telephone at 203-336-6810 or via email at[info@ronhazelton.com](mailto:info@ronhazelton.com)._  _If, at any time, you wish to change your contact information or opt out of future contacts with us, you may also inform us via telephone or email._
